ED
Iwase
はい
港浦です お疲れさま
Hello?
It's Miura. Good evening.
お疲れさまです
Good evening.
いきなりで申し訳ないが
Sorry for getting straight to the point,
今週の本ちゃん 15位だった
but it was 15th in the final rankings this week.
15位
15th?
班長にも「作画が新妻君じゃなかったら
とっくに終わってるぞ」って
Even my team leader said that if it
weren't for Niizuma Eiji doing the art,
it would have been canceled a long time ago.
今 FAXでもらった原作読んだけど なんか暗いんだよね
I read the script you faxed in,
and it's kinda dark.
新妻君も 最近 面白くないと言ってる
Niizuma also said that he's been finding it boring recently.
書き直します
I'll rewrite it.
いや 申し訳ないけど 作画の方で何とかしてもらうよ
Sorry, but I'll get him to make up for it with the art somehow.
まあ 今回「CROW」最終回で
表を持ってかれたってのもあるけど
Well, CROW's final chapter did
take away some votes from you.
岩瀬君は もう読んだ
Have you read it yet?
ほんとすごいよ 新妻エイジは
Ending
Color Pages
at page 31!
Niizuma Eiji is really something!
じゃあ 次は少年マンガらしく
スカッと明るい話をよろしく頼むよ
All right, next time I'll be counting on you for a bright, refreshing story more suited to shounen manga!
End of call
yu
me
Dreams, dreams, dreams, dreams
ka
na
e
ru
ta
bi
ko
wa
re
te
yu
ku
me
As soon as I reach my goals, it all falls through again
na
ze
so
re
de
mo
ma
ta
So why do I run...
bo
ku
wa
sa
ga
su
ha
shi
ri
tsu
zu
ke
ru
...and search in spite of that?
hi
sa
shi
bu
ri
ni
de
atta
We met after such a long time
"
fu
n
i
ki
ka
watta?"
"Has the mood changed for us?"
tsu
ki
hi
wa
na
ga
re
ta
da
rou
So much time has passed
"
a
no
ko
ro
no
ho
u
ga
ta
no
shi
so
u
"
"It seemed like more fun back then"
ta
ku
sa
n
na
ku
shi
ta
We've lost so much
so
n
na
ko
to
wa
ki
zu
i
te
ru
n
da
I already know that, though
sa
ke
bi
tsu
zu
ke
ro
mo
ga
ki
tsu
zu
ke
ro
Don't stop screaming, don't stop struggling
da
re
no
ta
me
ni
na
n
ka
mou
i
da
rou?
You've done enough for others
ma
da
tsu
ta
e
i
ko
to
ga
a
ru
ma
da
I still, still have something I haven't told you yet
yu
me
no
sa
ki
ni
wa
yu
me
shi
ka
na
i
Beyond each of my dreams lies yet another dream
本字幕由诸神字幕组(kamigami.org)出品 仅供交流学习之用 禁止用于商业用途
---诸神字幕组---
台本: 共由         翻译: 新人&poopy       繁化: 烨语
校对：绫女       时间轴：那年夏天
Zombies and Demons
Man, I can't believe CROW ended.
「CROW」終わっちゃったな
ショックだよな
That really shocked me.
にしても 「CROW」を終わらせて「NATURAL」は描いてるって
I'm telling you, those guys are pulling our legs by ending CROW and keeping NATURAL.
逆だよな 逆
「NATURAL」今回もクソつまんねえ
This week's NATURAL is so damn boring, too.
俺もう読んでないし
I haven't even read it yet.
マジで
Really?
読者も担当も新妻さんも「NATURAL」を必要としてない
The readers, the editors, and Niizuma, too...
They don't need NATURAL.
高木君との間にも 大きな差が
And there's a big gap between Takagi and I.
もうどうすればいいか分からない
I don't know what to do anymore.
Takagi Akito
無理
I can't.
はい 蒼樹です
Hi, this is Aoki.
ユリターン この店セルフだけど　ホント　紅茶美味しいです…
Yuri!
This restaurant is self-serve, but their tea's really good!
平丸さん 今電話中だから
Hiramaru, I'm on the phone right now.
すみません ユリタン
Sorry, Yuri.
もしもし ごめんなさい
Hello? I'm sorry about that.
すみません かけ直します
Sorry, I'll call back.
世に出たマンガで 一番すごいと思う作品ですか
Huh?
What do we think is the best manga in the world?
好きな作品とすごい作品ではまた違ってきますが
There's a difference between what manga I think is the best, and what manga is my favorite,
強いて1つと言うのなら
but if I had to pick one, I'd say it's Tezuka's Phoenix.
僕は手塚先生の「火の鳥」でしょうね
私はやっぱり「ベルサイユのばら」と「ガラスの仮面」かな
I'd have to say The Rose of Versailles and Glass Mask.
僕は断然「SLAM DUNK」です
I'm for SLAM DUNK all the way!
好きなマンガ聞くだけで その人の人柄分かるよな
You can really tell a lot about someone by asking them what manga they like.
うん
Yeah.
サイコーは「あしたのジョー」だよな
You'd say Ashita no Joe, right?
好きなマンガならそうだけど
If you're asking me what my favorite manga is, then yeah.
俺もすごいマンガとなると 違ってくるかも
But I would also give a different answer if
you're asking me what I think is the best one.
えっ 何
What is it, then?
「はだしのゲン」
Barefoot Gen.
小さい頃ここで読んで その夜眠れなかったのを覚えてる
When I was a kid, I remember reading it here and not being able to sleep that night.
それこそ 読み継がれていかなければいけない作品ですね
That's the kind of manga you can't put down until you're done reading it.
こういう話してると
When we talk about those, I can't help but feel that our own manga pales in comparison.
自分たちの描いてる作品が 少し情けなく思えてくる
時代とか人気ばかり追いかけた作品じゃなくて
I don't want to make something that's just popular during its own time.
時間がたっても 名作として読まれる作品
を残したい みたいな
I want to leave behind something that'll still be
regarded as a masterpiece many years from now.
Well, something like that.
エイジはそれをやろうとしている
That's what Eiji is trying to do.
「ジャック」で1番じゃなく
The next one I write won't just be the best manga in Jack...
世に出たマンガで1番のマンガです
It'll be the best manga ever written!
あれ 蒼樹さんからだ
Oh? It's from Aoki.
た 高木です
Th-This is Takagi.
はい
Yes.
秋名 ああ 岩瀬の事ですね
Akina?
Oh, Iwase?
岩瀬
Iwase?
別に何も聞いてませんけど
No, I haven't heard anything.
そうですか
I see.
どうかしたんですか
Is something wrong?
1週間前 秋名さんから電話があったんですが
Akina called me a week ago,
すぐ切られてしまって
but hung up quickly afterwards.
気になって 何度かかけてみたんですけど 出てくれなくて
I got concerned and called her many times,
but she wouldn't pick up.
担当の港浦さんには
Have you tried her editor, Miura?
山久さんに聞いてもらいました
I had Yamashita ask him.
そうしたら 秋名さん「もう書かない」って
He said that Akina... wouldn't write anymore.
えっ 「書かない」って 岩瀬がそう言ったんですか
Huh?!
She won't write anymore?!
Did Iwase say that herself?
部屋を訪ねても 返事もしてくれないそうです
It seems that even when he visited her
apartment, she wouldn't answer her door.
ご迷惑かもしれませんが
彼女が一番心を開けるのは高木さんじゃないかと
I didn't want to trouble you, but I believe you're the one
she opens up to the most.
分かりました
Okay.
知らせてくれてありがとうございます
Thanks for letting me know.
何 「書かない」って どういう事
What? What do you mean "she won't write"?
香耶ちゃん 岩瀬の所に行ってもいいよな
Kaya.
I can drop by Iwase's place, right?
何で 秋人さんが
Why do you have to go?
心配だからに決まってるだろ
Because I'm worried about her, obviously!
部屋に何日もこもって 返事もないらしい
Apparently she's been holed up in her
apartment for days and won't answer anyone.
勝手に「書かない」って言ってるんでしょ
She said herself that she wouldn't write anymore, right? Iwase is so selfish.
岩瀬 わがまますぎ
俺が行ってくる
I'll go.
サイコー
Saikou?
大丈夫 俺シュージンの気持ちも分かってるつもりだし
It's okay. I know how Shuujin feels about this.
住所と連絡先知ってるの
Do you know her address and contact info?
港浦さんに聞けばいいだけだ
I'll just ask Miura.
大体 真城 岩瀬とろくに話した事ないんじゃ
But Mashiro, you've never really talked to her before.
そんなの関係ない
That doesn't matter.
エイジの言ったように
「ジャック」で競ってるライバルであって仲間
Like Eiji said, the rivals we compete with in Jack are also our friends.
それには変わりないんだ
There's no changing that fact.
Iwase
秋名君 俺が悪かった
Akina, I was wrong!
新妻君と僕と また3人で「NATURAL」を立て直そう
Let's fix up NATURAL with the
three of us: you, me and Niizuma!
だから 返事だけでも
So please, just answer me...
港浦さん
Miura!
真城君
Mashiro?
岩瀬は
How's Iwase?
中にいるとは思うんだが 返事をしてくれないんだよ
I think she's inside,
but she won't answer.
真城です
It's Mashiro.
岩瀬 返事をしてくれ
Iwase, answer me!
インターホンに出てくれ
Get on the intercom!
10分たっても返事がなければ
警察に訳を話してドアを開けてもらう
If you don't answer in the next ten minutes,
I'll call the police and get them to break down this door.
岩瀬 返事しろ
Iwase, answer me!
岩瀬
うるさいぞ いい加減にしろ
Iwase!
Keep it down! You're too loud!
岩瀬 岩瀬
Iwase! Iwase!
す すいません
S-Sorry.
岩瀬
います
Iwa—
I'm here.
よかった
Thank goodness.
ありがとう
Thanks.
じゃあ もう大声は出さない
I won't shout anymore.
でも 話は聞いてくれ
But listen to what I have to say.
やめたければ やめればいい
If you want to quit, then quit.
何言ってんだ 真城君
What are you saying, Mashiro?!
でも それなら ちゃんと港浦さんや編集長と話して
However, in order to do that you'll need to talk to Miura and the Chief Editor
筋を通してから やめるべきだろ
and go through the proper procedures first.
これじゃ子供だ
The way you're acting right now is childish.
頭のいい岩瀬のする事じゃない
It's not something the smart Iwase would do.
やっぱり私は 亜城木夢叶にとってどうでもいい存在
I knew it...
I don't matter to Ashirogi Mutou.
やめてほしくないけど
I don't want you to quit,
岩瀬がそう決めたのなら しかたない
but if that's what you've decided, then there's nothing I can do.
シュージンは
岩瀬が同じ世界に来て競ってくれてる事に感謝してる
Shuujin is grateful that you came into his
world and competed with him on his terms.
うれしく思ってるんだ
He was happy to think of you
ライバルとして
as a rival.
ライバル
A rival?
原作者として一番のライバルになってくれた事も
今となっては感謝してるし
I'm thankful that you're my greatest rival as an author,
and I think of you as one of my comrades
who holds the same goals in regards to Jack.
「ジャック」で同じ志を持つ仲間だと思ってる
今度は 俺から言わせてもらおう
This time, I'll be the one to say it.
互いを励みにして頑張ろう
Let's encourage each other, and do our best!
俺だって そうやってシュージンのライバルとして
I was glad, too.
As Shuujin's rival, you gave him
some motivation to keep improving.
刺激になってくれるのはうれしい
でも それは
But...
俺たちの勝手な希望で
that's only what we hoped you'd be for us.
これから先やるかやらないかは 岩瀬自身が決める事
It's up to you whether you'll keep going or not.
俺が言いたいのはそれだけだ
That's all I have to say.
じゃあ 秋名君 また明日来る
Well then, Akina,
I'll drop by again tomorrow.
岩瀬 頼みがある
Iwase, do me a favor.
ドアを開けてくれ
Open the door.
虚勢でいいから 元気なところを見せてくれ
Show me that you're okay, even if you have to fake it!
頼む 岩瀬
Please, Iwase!
電話くれたのに
気持ちに気付いてあげられなくて ごめんなさい
I'm sorry for not realizing how you felt, even though you called me.
意地ばっか張ってねえで 福田組に入っちまえよ
Stop being so stubborn and join Team Fukuda already.
そうすりゃ一人で悩む事もなくなるぜ
If you do, you won't be alone with your worries anymore.
ほら 秋人さん
Come on, Akito.
どうしてもやめるって言うなら 止めない
If you want to quit so badly, I won't stop you.
「CROW」っていう巨大なライバルを失ったばかりなのに
But I just lost a strong rival in CROW,
原作者としての最大のライバルまで 失いたくないけどな
so I don't want to lose my greatest rival as an author as well.
おい
Hey.
あなたたちに負けるわけにはいきません
I can't afford to lose to you guys.
また 上に行ってみせます
I'll prove that I can rise to the top again.
あなたたちのように つるんだりせずにです
All by myself, without joining a team!
それでこそ岩瀬だ
Yeah!
That's Iwase for you!
言ってくれるじゃねえか
Yeah.
Nice proclamation.
今後の「NATURAL」楽しみにしてます
I'm looking forward to the next NATURAL.
おい 佐々木
Hey, Sasaki.
ちょっと来～い
Come here.
はい
Yes, sir.
編集長が役員室に呼ばれた
The Chief Editor just got called to the executive room...
まさか 編集長代わるんじゃ
Maybe... the Chief is getting replaced?
4月から「必勝ジャック」が本格的に始動するしな
Well, Hissho Jack is finally getting underway in April.
そういえば最近 編集長気持ち悪いくらい優しいですよね
Speaking of which, the Chief has
been so nice lately it's almost creepy.
「NATURAL」持ち直したな よくやった
You've helped NATURAL recover. Great job.
初めてですよ あんな事
He's never said anything like that to me before.
僕も この前「頑張れ」って声かけられました
A while ago, he called out "Do your best!" to me, too.
瓶子 ちょっと来～い
Heishi, come here.
はい
Yes, sir.
次の編集長は瓶子さん
Heishi is the next Chief Editor?!
「遊☆戯☆王」はでかいからな
Yu-Gi-Oh! is big, after all.
瓶子副編集長が編集長になったら
If Assistant Chief Editor Heishi becomes the new Chief Editor...
班長の誰かが副編集長に繰り上げ
...then one team leader will be promoted to Assistant Chief Editor!
Editorial Department
Shounen Jack
Jack SQ
X Jack
結局 佐々木編集長と中野班長は
実績が買われて「必勝ジャック」に異動
In the end, Chief Editor Sasaki and team leader Nakano
were transfered to Hissho Jack based on the strength of their accomplishments.
「週刊少年ジャック」の方は瓶子さんが編集長
As for Weekly Shounen Jack,
Heishi is now Chief Editor,
相田さんが副編か
and Aida is the Assistant Chief.
だな
おいおい 大事な事忘れてるぞ
You bet!
Hey, hey! You're forgetting something important here!
俺が班長 俺が班長
I'm a team leader now! A team leader!
はいはい
Yeah, yeah.
雄二郎
Yuujirou.
あ はい
Yes?
明日 時間取れるか
Can you make some time tomorrow?
多分 大丈夫かと
I think so.
今回の報告もかねて 各作家さんに挨拶しておきたいんだが
In light of this news, I'd like to pay my respects to all the authors.
新妻君 どうだ
What's Niizuma's schedule?
Niizuma
Eiji Ltd
いきなりだが
I know this is sudden, but at the end of the
month, I will be transferring to Hissho Jack.
私は今月いっぱいで「必勝ジャック」に異動という事になった
ちなみに 僕は班長になる
And also, I'm going to become a team leader.
新妻君 編集長の前だから
Niizuma...
You're in front of the Chief Editor!
今までありがとうございました
Thank you for all you've done for me.
青森まで来てもらった時は 本当にうれしかったです
I was happy when you came all the way out to Aomori to see me.
あの時も 僕と編集長の2人だったな
It was me and the Chief back then, too.
もう8年以上前か
Was that really eight years ago?
いきなり「一番人気の作家になったら」
When you suddenly said "If I become the No. 1 author, give me the right to end one manga,"
「マンガを1つ終わらせる権利をくれ」と言われた時は
生意気な子だと思った
I thought you were just a cheeky little kid.
だが 今では 立派な「ジャック」の看板作家になってくれて
But now you've gone on to become one of the most prominent authors of Jack.
これからも期待している
I'm still expecting great things out of you.
まだ 本当の1番にはなってませんけど
Best in
the World
I'm not really the best yet,
Best in
the World
世界一のマンガを描きます
Best in
the World
but I'm going to make the best manga in the world!
Best in
the World
まだあるです
I have more.
いや もういいって
Um, that's enough.
あくまでも目標です
It's just a goal of his.
新妻君の事は 何も心配してない
I'm not worried about you at all, Niizuma.
新雑誌の編集長をしながら 見守らせてもらうよ
As the chief editor of a new
magazine, I'll be watching over you.
はい
Yes.
でも その前に です
But before that...
編集長がわざわざ挨拶に来るって 緊張するな
The Chief Editor is coming all the way out here to see us.
I'm so nervous!
大丈夫だって 服部さんも来るんだし
It'll be okay. Hattori will be with him.
俺たち さんざんわがまま言って 迷惑かけたもんな
We've been plenty selfish and caused a ton of trouble for him.
入院した時に 休載しないって言い張ったり
Like when I insisted on not going on hiatus when I was in the hospital,
「タント」やめたいとかな
and when we wanted to quit Tanto.
その前には 連載経験ある契約作家なのに
勝手に月例賞出したり
And before that, when we knowingly entered the amateur prize contest,
even though we were experienced authors under contract.
やべえな
This is bad.
この機会にちゃんと謝らないとな
We have to use this opportunity to properly apologize!
来た
He's here!
お疲れさま
Good afternoon.
お疲れさまです
G-Good afternoon!
失礼する
Excuse me for intruding.
ど どうぞ こちらへ
O-Over here, please.
タバコのにおいはしないんだな
I don't smell cigarettes.
僕たちは吸いませんから
We don't smoke.
そうか 「超ヒーロー伝説」の時も担当を
Oh, right.
He's been here before as the editor of Super Hero Legend.
「週刊少年ジャック」の編集長ではなくなる事が
決まったから言うが
Because I'll no longer be the chief editor of Weekly Shounen Jack,
生前の川口たろうに頼まれた事があった
I can tell you about the favor that Kawaguchi Tarou asked of me when he was still alive.
連載会議 通りませんでした
You didn't pass through the serialization committee.
そうですか
I see.
でも 手応えはありました
They gave us some feedback, though.
次の会議に向けて頑張りましょう
Let's try for the next committee.
そうですね
You're right.
ヒット作を何本も出せる作家になって
タカを待っていたいですから
I want to become an author who can put out one hit after another as I wait for Taka.
タカ
Taka?
甥っ子です
My nephew.
俺に憧れてマンガ家になるって
He looks up to me and says he'll be a manga artist.
そんなあいつの夢を壊したくないんです
I don't want to let him down.
甥っ子さん いくつなんですか
How old is your nephew?
まだ 小学生です
He's still in elementary school.
でも マンガを描くのが本当に好きで
He really loves drawing manga, though,
ここに来てよく描いてますよ
and comes here often to draw.
ヒーローマンですか
It's Heroman.
川口さんより ずっと上手ですね
He's way better than you are.
勘弁して下さいよ
Give me a break.
でも あいつは俺なんかよりずっとすごいマンガ家になれる
But he can become a far better
manga artist than I could ever be.
そう思うんです
That's what I think.
だから それまでは現役でいたい
So, I want to be active until then.
そして いつか2人で「ジャック」に連載ですね
So that one day you can both be
serialized in Jack at the same time?
あいつがプロになった時は よろしくお願いします
When he goes professional, take care of him.
おじさんがそんな事を
Uncle Tarou said that?
編集部で服部と打ち合わせをしている2人の中学生の1人が
When I learned that one of the two middle school
students Hattori was meeting at the editing department
その川口たろうの甥だと知った時には 驚いた
was Kawaguchi Tarou's nephew, I was surprised.
いや うれしかったよ
Or rather, I was pleased.
そんな事情もあってか 冷静でいられない時が多かった
It was because of those circumstances
that I often couldn't keep my cool when it came to you.
すまなかった
I'm sorry.
そんな
Not at all!
僕たちの方がいろいろ謝ろうと思ってたんです
We're the ones who have things to apologize for!
そ そうです
That's right!
いや 今思えば 真城君が入院した時
No, now that I think about it,
deciding to put TRAP on hold when you were
hospitalized until you graduated school was too strict.
高校を卒業するまで「TRAP」を休載させるという判断は
厳しすぎた
「PCP」が新妻君の作品と肩を並べなければ
打ち切るというのも そうだ
The same goes for saying that PCP would be
canceled if you couldn't draw even with Niizuma.
それをよく跳ね返してくれた
You turned those restrictions right back on me.
いえ その試練を与えて頂いたからこそ
今の僕たちがあるんです
No, it's because you gave us those trials that we are who we are now.
本当にお世話になりました
We are truly in your debt!
ありがとうございました
Thank you!
それは大げさだ
You're exaggerating.
今の君たちがあるのは 君たちの実力だ
You're who you are now because of your own abilities.
本当によくここまでになってくれた
You've done very well to get this far.
川口たろうの事もあって
Because of Kawaguchi Tarou,
どうしても君たちを特別扱いしてしまったのかもしれない
I would've probably treated you differently no matter what.
甘やかす方向にではないがな
Not in a nice way, though.
それが本当なら ひいきしてもらったと考えます
If that's true, then I'd like to think that you favored us.
それが 僕たちのためになったんですから
Because it was for our own sakes.
だが それもここまでだ
But that's all over with.
もう君たちは「ジャック」の看板作家 亜城木夢叶
You are already prolific authors in Jack as Ashirogi Mutou.
そして君たちが超えるべきは 新妻エイジ
And the one you must overcome is Niizuma Eiji.
新妻君はすごいマンガ家だが
Niizuma is an amazing manga author,
今 新妻君以上になれる者がいるとすれば
君たちだと思っている
but if there's anyone who can surpass him,
I think it would be you two.
いや これも もしかしたらひいきかもしれないな
No, perhaps I'm just favoring you again.
いえ ひいきじゃないと証明してみせます
No, we'll show you that you're not!
必ず
For sure!
そうか 期待している
I see.
I'll be expecting that, then.
先日 新妻君の所へ行った時
When I went to visit Niizuma the other day,
「新作を用意している」と言っていた
he said he was getting his new manga ready.
私が編集長でいる間に 見せてくれるそうだ
He said he'll be ready to show it to me before I transfer.
エイジがついに新作を
Eiji's finally got a new manga.
それも 編集長が代わるまでになんて
And it'll be ready before the Chief leaves!
新妻君 編集長にあんな事言ったけど
Best in
the World
Niizuma,
I know you said that to the Chief,
本当は 何描くかまだ決めてないんだろ どうするの
but you really haven't decided what to do yet, have you?
What're you going to do?
いえ もう決まってますけど
I've already decided, though.
本当に 決まってるの
You really have?
何 どんな話
On what? What kind of story is it?
俺たちもやろうぜ 新作
Let's do one too! A new manga!
「やろうぜ」って簡単に言うなよ
That's not as easy as you make it sound.
いや 実は 前にサイコーが描いたキャラから思いついた
No, I actually thought of something
after looking at that character you drew.
いけそうな話があるんだ
I have a story that'll work!
マジ
For real?!
マジだ
Yeah!
で このキャラからどんな話思いついたんだよ
So, what kind of story did you think up for this character?
主人公は 悪魔の力をもらう
The protagonist will receive power from a demon,
この姿は 悪魔の力を使う時
and he'll look like this while he's using the demon's powers.
だから 人間バージョンのキャラも作って もちろん変身前な
So, you'll need to make a human version of him for when he isn't transformed.
悪魔の力
A demon's power?
悪魔から授かった力で
自分の思想を他人に伝染させる事ができるんだ
Using the power he received,
he can force his thoughts onto other people.
シュージンの考える原作っぽいな
It sounds like just your kind of story.
主人公は 自分の考えこそ全て正しいと思い込んでる
The protagonist is an all-around excellent high school student,
あらゆる面で優秀でバカな高校生
but he's actually a fool for believing that his ideals and way of thinking is correct.
自分と同じ思想をより多くの人間が持つ事で
世の中が良くなると信じ切っている
He's convinced that the world will become a
better place if more people think like he does.
やっている事は洗脳だが 自分は正義だと思っている
He's brainwashing people, but he thinks he's doing the right thing.
なるほど ダークヒーローか
I get it!
He's a dark hero!
ダークヒーロー
A dark hero?
見てみないと 何とも言えないけど
I can't say much without seeing it,
僕としては あんまり少年向けじゃないというか
but it doesn't sound very shounen-like to me.
多くの人に支持されるのは難しいというか
I can't imagine many people would support that...
主人公 どんなの
What's the protagonist like?
ゾンビですけど
He's a zombie!
悪魔の力をもらうダークヒーローか
A dark hero with a demon's powers?
悪魔なんだから黒が多い方が
Because he's a demon, it's probably best to add some black.
ダークヒーロー
Dark hero...
邪道バトル
Unorthodox battle manga...
人間と
Human and standard unorthodox...
王道 邪道
「疑探偵TRAP」
Detective TRAP, PCP.
「PCP」
「この世は金と知恵」
This World is Money and Intelligence.
そうか
I've got it!
おう 何
Yeah, what?
シュージン 思いっきりエグいの書けよな
Shuujin, you're gonna portray him as a really dark character, right?
はあ
Huh?
主人公は思いっきりいかれてて
He'll be completely insane!
気に入らない悪人は全て抹殺すべきくらいの
考えを持ってるやつ
Make him think that all evildoers he doesn't like should be eliminated!
それじゃ 完全に悪に見えちゃうんじゃ
Huh?! He'll look totally evil, then.
大丈夫だって
It's fine! If we go too far, Hattori will prune it back for us.
やりすぎてたら 服部さんが削ってくれるんだから
俺たちは変に自重しないで 思いっきりやっちゃおうぜ
We shouldn't be so cautious! Let's go all out!
O-Okay.
Niizuma
Eiji Ltd
もうネーム出来たって
You've got a storyboard already?!
はい
Yes!
ちょっと 読ませてもらっていいか
Can I read it?
あとは キャラデザです
All that's left is the character design!
ゾンビって言っても一目で読者が好きになってくれないとですから
Even though he's a zombie, the
readers have to like him immediately!
言わなくても分かってるのが すごいよな
I'm gonna make a scary horror story.
He already knows without me having to tell him. Amazing.
まだネームなのに この迫力
This intensity from just a storyboard!
ワクワクして鳥肌が立つ
It's so exciting that I'm getting goosebumps!
「ゾンビ」って聞いた時は 正直ピンとこなかったけど
すごいよ
I didn't really get it at first when you said "zombie," but this is amazing!
人間の女の子に恋するっていうのも面白い
Making him fall in love with a
human girl is an interesting idea!!
ヒロインも魅力的にします
I'll make the heroine appealing!
単純なストーリーだけど 「CROW」にはなかった人間ドラマが入ってる
It's a simple story, but there's a human drama here that wasn't in CROW.
これは「CROW」を超えるかも
This might even surpass CROW!
やっぱり 新妻君は天才だ
Niizuma really is a genius.
マジで世界も夢じゃないかも
Maybe being No.1 in the world isn't just a dream!
どう
How is it?
うん エグい
It's dark, all right.
主人公の思想はかなり不快になる
The protagonist's ideals are pretty disturbing.
そこまで不快になっちゃ駄目だろ
It's not good for it to be that dark, right?
駄目だよ
Nope.
サイコーがエグくしろって言ったんだろ
You're the one who told me to do this!
シュージン これ
Shuujin, here.
何 新しい悪魔
What? A new demon?
そっ 正義の悪魔
Yes.
A demon of justice.
えっ 正義
Justice?
つうか かっこいいな
He's cool!
で これどうすんだ
So, what do I do with this?
「この世は金と知恵」は
「NEXT」でエイジの王道バトルに負けた
This World is Money and Intelligence lost to Eiji's standard battle manga in NEXT.
「PCP」もまだ本当のトップになれてないし
PCP never really made it to the top either.
結局 「CROW」には勝てなかった
In the end, it never did beat CROW.
「疑探偵TRAP」も
Detective TRAP didn't either.
やっぱり 少年マンガらしくないんだ
It's because they don't follow the shounen manga archetype.
邪道の限界
It's the limitation of an unorthodox style.
何を 今更
What's this all of a sudden?
シュージンは邪道が合ってるし エグいのもうまい
An unorthodox style suits you, and you're good at dark and disturbing stuff, too.
この原作も面白い
This script is good,
でも 邪道のままじゃ限界がある
but there's a limit to how far we can go with just unorthodox.
まま じゃ
"Just"?
そう
Yes!
だから 本当の王道の正義キャラを出す
That's why we'll introduce a real mainstream character of justice.
悪魔の力を悪として使う少年と
A young man who uses a demon's power for evil,
悪魔の力を正義のために使う少年の
and a young man who uses a demon's power for good.
ダブル主人公
Two protagonists!
その2人が戦う
正義を出す事で本当の王道バトルマンガになる
By bringing justice into the mix, this
will become a standard battle manga.
今までの限界から抜けられる
We can break through the limitations we've had up till now!
サイコーが すげえエグいのにしろって言ったのは
この考えがあったからか
So you told me to make it really
disturbing because you thought of this?
Yeah.
黒悪魔は 思いっきり悪く見せた方が面白い
It'll be interesting to show just how evil the black demon can get.
白悪魔は「他人に自分の思想を
植え付けるなんて絶対に許せない」ってキャラ
And the white demon will never forgive him for planting his thoughts on others.
なるほど
I see.
思想と思想の戦い
It'll be a battle of ideals.
それを植え付けられた人間たちの戦い
A battle of the humans on whom these ideals were implanted.
そして ダブル主人公の戦い
And a battle of these two protagonists!
うん
Yeah!
そして最後に勝つのは真の正義
And true justice will win in the end!
それでこそ 少年マンガ
That's what shounen manga is all about!
今までと違い スケールもでかい
The scale is different from anything we've done before!
ありがとな サイコー
Thanks, Saikou!
相当面白くなるよ
It's gotten a lot better!
これでエイジと勝負だ
Let's fight against Eiji with this!
結局 王道バトル描く事になったな
So we'll end up doing a standard battle manga after all.
Yeah.
もう王道の新妻エイジ
邪道の亜城木夢叶なんて考えは終わりだ
It's the end of thinking "Ashirogi does
unorthodox and Niizuma does standard."
遠回りしたわけじゃない
We didn't take any detours to get here.
今の俺たちだから描ける
We can draw this because we are who we are now, and no one else could do this.
俺たちにしか描けない
亜城木夢叶ならではの王道バトルだ
A standard battle manga that only Ashirogi can do!
do
u
shi
te
da
ro...
i
tsu
mo
so
u
sa
Why, I wonder?
chi
ka
zu
ku
ta
bi
ka
ra
ma
wa
ri
no
yu
me
Whenever I am close to fulfilling my goals, all effort becomes fruitless
ma
e
wo
mu
i
te
shi
ga
mi
tsu
i
te
sou
su
ko
shi
zu
tsu
We walk ahead, hold each other, and with little things
ya
ku
so
no
a
ba
sho
he
to
sa
e
ai
na
ga
ra
we support each other to reach what we promised
ji
shi
n
ga
ta
ri
na
i
to
ki
wa
mu
ne
ni
te
wo
a
te
When we lack confidence, we put a hand to our heart
bo
ku
ra
ga
tsu
zu
t
ta
pe
e
ji
yo
mi
ka
e
so
u
and reread the pages we assembled into a story
kyo
u
ma
de
so
shi
te
a
su
he
to
tsu
zu
i
te
yu
ku
no
sa
They lead up to today and continue into the morrow
ta
i
se
tsu
na
yu
me
ga
ka
na
u
so
no
hi
ma
de
We will always be ourselves
a
ri
no
ma
bo
ku
ra
de
zu
tto...
until the day that our dreams come true
亜城木君と新妻君 どっちが勝つかな
Next Time
Preview
Who will win, Ashirogi or Niizuma?
負けませんよ 雄二郎さん
We won't lose, Yuujirou!
班長と呼べ 班長と
Call me Team Leader!
次回 週刊と月刊
Next time: Weekly and Monthly.
Weekly and
Monthly
夢は 思いをぶつけるところから始まる
Dreams start when you collide feelings with one another!